gsalr.com 2019-06-09

# Privacy Policy | gsalr.com

**Effective Date: June 1, 2007**

### Privacy Policy

gsalr.com values the users of our website (the "Website"). Your privacy and trust are very important to us. We recognize that you may be concerned about our collection, use, and disclosure of the personal information that we collect when you use the Website. This Privacy Policy describes the information that we collect from you, how we collect this information, and what we do with it after we collect it. By using the Website you are accepting the practices described in this Privacy Policy. If you have any questions or comments regarding this Privacy Policy, please contact us at [support@gsalr.com](mailto:support@gsalr.com).

### Personal Information

The entry of personally identifiable information ("Personal Information"), such as email or postal address, is completely voluntary and optional. We use Personal Information only for services you have requested. We will not disclose Personal Information to any third parties.

Whenever we obtain your Personal Information, we use commercially reasonable efforts to protect it from unauthorized access or disclosure. However, we are not insurers of the security of your Personal Information. Accordingly, we assume no liability for any disclosure of data due to errors in transmission, unauthorized third party access or other acts of third parties, or acts or omissions beyond our reasonable control.

We provide you the opportunity to opt-out of having your Personal Information used for certain purposes. For example, if you subscribe to a mailing list, you may unsubscribe by following the instructions included in each newsletter, or by emailing us at [support@gsalr.com](mailto:support@gsalr.com).

### Non-Personal Information

We also collect non-personal information from you, such as your browser type, the URL of the previous website you visited, your ISP, operating system, and your Internet protocol (IP) Address. We may disclose non-personal information, in aggregate form, to potential strategic partners, advertisers, investors, customers, and others. You may not opt-out of the sharing of this information. However, it cannot be used to identify you personally.

### Third Party Websites

You may be able to access third party websites directly from the Website. This Privacy Policy does not apply when you access third party websites. We cannot control how third parties may use Personal Information you disclose to them, so you should carefully review the privacy policy of any third party website you visit before using it or disclosing your Personal Information to its provider.
